What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Why don't you be with your good friend,
لماذا لا تكون مع صديقك العزيز ،
Wu Wancheng.
وو Wancheng.
You're still angry.
ما زلت غاضبًا.
It's just a matter of fact.
إنها مجرد حقيقة.
You're injured. Don't stay here.
أنت مصاب.  لا تبق هنا.
Come back to the dorm with me
أعود إلى المسكن معي
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
No.
لا.
I'm not going back.
لن أعود.
I can't make up for my broken heart.
لا أستطيع أن أعوض قلبي المكسور.
I want to make
اريد ان افعل
a clean break with you.
استراحة نظيفة معك.
Make a clean break.
اصنع استراحة نظيفة.
Okay,
تمام،
I'll tell Brother Wu then.
سأخبر الأخ وو بعد ذلك.
He said you lied to him,
قال أنك كذبت عليه ،
but those materials are not mine at all.
لكن هذه المواد ليست لي على الإطلاق.
But you secretly got them from the black market.
لكنك حصلت عليها سرا من السوق السوداء.
No,
لا،
Calm down.
إهدئ.
Let go.
اتركه.
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
But I still don't understand,
لكن ما زلت لا أفهم ،
why didn't you tell Brother Wu the truth?
لماذا لم تخبر الاخ وو بالحقيقة؟
I don't want anyone to know that
لا أريد أن يعرف أحد ذلك
I'm working on an invention,
أنا أعمل على اختراع ،
So what if it's a research invention?
إذن ماذا لو كان اختراعًا بحثيًا؟
To be honest, in my opinion,
لأكون صادقًا ، في رأيي ،
your research and inventions are very useful.
إن أبحاثك واختراعاتك مفيدة جدًا.
Really?
حقًا؟
Yeah,
نعم،
for example,
على سبيل المثال،
the artificial wings you invented,
الأجنحة الاصطناعية التي اخترعتها ،
And that
وذلك
head-mounted umbrella,
مظلة محمولة على الرأس
I use it every time it rains.
أستخدمه في كل مرة تمطر فيها.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
Brother Qi knows me best.
يعرفني الأخ Qi أفضل.
Cut it out.
اقطعها.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
This is my secret recipe.
هذه هي وصفتي السرية.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
There is no trace in writing.
لا يوجد أثر في الكتابة.
Color when exposed to heat,
اللون عند تعرضه للحرارة ،
usually in the market,
عادة في السوق ،
They all sell at this price.
كلهم يبيعون بهذا السعر.
50 taels,
50 تيل ،
Today, my classmates
اليوم زملائي
found a treasure. Ladies and gentlemen,
وجدت كنزا.  السيدات والسادة،
I can't afford it.
لا أستطيع تحمله.
10 taels?
10 تايل؟
I can't afford it either.
لا أستطيع تحمله أيضًا.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
اعذرني.  اعذرني.
It's amazing.
شيء مذهل.
-I want one. -I want one.
-أريد واحد.  -أريد واحد.
Okay, Mr. Chen. One bottle.
حسنًا ، سيد تشين.  زجاجة واحدة.
Anyone else wants it?
أي شخص آخر يريد ذلك؟
Hold on tight.
تمسك بإحكام.
I'll have one, too.
سآخذ واحدة أيضًا.
Don't worry. Take it yourself.
لا تقلق.  خذها بنفسك.
-Give it to me. -This is yours.
-اعطني اياه.  -هذا لك.
Well
حسنًا
Okay, this is yours.
حسنًا ، هذا لك.
This is onion juice.
هذا عصير بصل.
What onion juice?
ما عصير البصل؟
This is the magic ink that I bought to develop color when heated.
هذا هو الحبر السحري الذي اشتريته لتطوير اللون عند تسخينه.
It cost 10 taels?
تكلف 10 تايل؟
Compensate me.
عوضني.
This is onion juice.
هذا عصير بصل.
Smell it yourself,
شمها بنفسك ،
The reason why the color appears when exposed to heat,
سبب ظهور اللون عند تعرضه للحرارة ،
is because of the plant material in onion juice,
بسبب المواد النباتية الموجودة في عصير البصل ،
The handwriting will only be displayed
سيتم عرض خط اليد فقط
when you zoom when it's hot.
عندما تقوم بالتكبير عندما يكون الجو حارًا.
Other plants also have the same effect.
نباتات أخرى لها نفس التأثير.
Do you think this thing is worth 10 taels?
هل تعتقد أن هذا الشيء يستحق 10 تايل؟
Give me two taels,
أعطني تيلان ،
and I'll make you ten bottles.
وسأصنع لك عشر زجاجات.
I'm a chemistry student,
أنا طالبة كيمياء
I can't be fooled by this kind of elementary school stuff,
لا يمكن أن يخدعني هذا النوع من مواد المدرسة الابتدائية ،
Two taels,
اثنان تيل
Tang Wenqi,
تانغ وينكي ،
You lied to me.
لقد كذبت علي
Pay me back.
رد الدين.
Well,
حسنًا،
listen to me. Listen to me,
استمع لي.  استمع لي،
I … I … I … I … I … Well.
أنا ... أنا ... أنا ... أنا ... أنا ... حسنًا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Refund! Refund! Refund!
استرداد!  استرداد!  استرداد!
Take it easy. Take it easy to refund the money.
خذها ببساطة.  خذها بسهولة لاسترداد الأموال.
Stop,
قف،
Chen Lan, Chen Lan, Chen Lan,
Chen Lan، Chen Lan، Chen Lan،
share it with them.
شاركها معهم.
Come on. One for each.
تعال.  واحد لكل.
Wu Wancheng,
وو وانشنغ ،
It's you again.
انه انت مرة اخرى.
I'm so unlucky when I meet you.
أنا غير محظوظ عندما ألتقي بك.
I haven't talked about you yet.
لم أتحدث عنك بعد.
My clothes,
ملابسي،
deserve it
تستحقها
Gosh, he hid private goods.
يا إلهي ، أخفى البضائع الخاصة.
He hid private goods too,
أخفى البضائع الخاصة أيضًا ،
Every time I met Wu Wancheng, I was unlucky,
في كل مرة أقابل فيها وو وانشنغ ، كنت غير محظوظ ،
and everything was ruined.
ودمر كل شيء.
Gosh, why is he back too?
يا إلهي ، لماذا عاد أيضًا؟
Why is he back?
لماذا عاد؟
Who closed the door in broad daylight?
من أغلق الباب في وضح النهار؟
Did my clothes
فعلت ملابسي
get stolen? This is
يسرق؟  هذا هو
Tang Wenqi,
تانغ وينكي ،
Oh no.
أوه لا.
Father must be here to catch me.
يجب أن يكون الأب هنا ليلحق بي.
Tang Wenqi.
تانغ وينكي.
Don't talk. Someone is
لا تتكلم.  احدهم
playing tricks on me in the Academy again.
لعب الحيل علي في الأكاديمية مرة أخرى.
I'll beat you to death today.
سأضربك حتى الموت اليوم.
You.
أنت.
You brat.
أنت شقي.
It's a mess.
هذه فوضى.
My father wants to catch me.
أبي يريد أن يمسك بي.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
What does it have to do with me?
ماذا يجب أن تفعل معي؟
You don't want me
انت لا تريدني
to misunderstand you?
لسوء فهمك؟
How could I misunderstand?
كيف يمكنني أن أسيء الفهم؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I said
انا قلت
Why are you blushing?
لماذا تحمر خجلا؟
No, I didn't.
لا ، لم أفعل.
And he said
و قال
it wasn't as popular as it was,
لم تكن شائعة كما كانت ،
You don't like men, do you?
أنت لا تحب الرجال ، أليس كذلك؟
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
You'll make trouble if you chase him away.
ستثير المتاعب إذا طاردته بعيدًا.
Why do you act like I'm right?
لماذا تتصرف وكأنني على حق؟
Let's go,
دعنا نذهب،
let's see what you've done to my room.
دعنا نرى ما فعلته بغرفتي.
Go, go, go.
إذهب! إذهب! إذهب.
I don't really like men, do I?
أنا لا أحب الرجال حقًا ، أليس كذلك؟
Impossible. Impossible.
مستحيل.  مستحيل.
My legs are numb.
ساقاي خدرتان.
Really?
حقًا؟
This door is broken.
هذا الباب مكسور.
Help! Is there anyone here?
يساعد!  هل من أحد هنا؟
Boss,
رئيس،
is that you?
هل هذا أنت؟
Come on, open the door.
تعال ، افتح الباب.
It's so late. I don't think there's anyone here.
لقد فات الوقت.  لا أعتقد أنه يوجد أحد هنا.
This is an upgraded and enhanced version I made.
هذه نسخة مطورة ومحسنة قمت بإنشائها.
I don't believe you can't blow up the modern times this time.
لا أعتقد أنه لا يمكنك تفجير العصر الحديث هذه المرة.
Chen Lan, can you do it? Try harder.
تشين لان ، هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟  بذل جهد أكبر.
You can't kick me.
لا يمكنك ركلني.
I've tried my best, boss.
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدي يا سيدي.
Why is it Tang Wenqi again?
لماذا هو Tang Wenqi مرة أخرى؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Boss,
رئيس،
You've suffered a lot, boss.
لقد عانيت كثيرًا يا رئيس.
Get a bucket of water. I
احصل على دلو من الماء.  أنا
… I want to take a bath.
… اريد ان استحم.
Okay, boss.
مدرب بخير.
I'll be right there.
سأكون هناك.
this time
هذا الوقت
Who is it?
من هذا؟
It's really not me.
إنه ليس أنا حقًا.
I haven't asked you yet.
أنا لم أسألك بعد.
Why did you admit it?
لماذا اعترفت بذلك؟
According to my investigation today,
حسب استقصائي اليوم ،
you were the only one who left the prison last night.
كنت الوحيد الذي غادر السجن الليلة الماضية.
Besides, you're the only one
علاوة على ذلك ، أنت الوحيد
who holds explosives in the Academy,
من يحمل متفجرات في الأكاديمية ،
More importantly,
أكثر أهمية،
I'm still at the toilet.
ما زلت في المرحاض.
I found a small footprint.
لقد وجدت بصمة صغيرة.
Of all the people in the Academy,
من بين كل الناس في الأكاديمية ،
the smallest one belongs to you.
أصغرها ملك لك.
So the truth is,
لذا فالحقيقة هي
the real murderer of the bombing is you.
أنت القاتل الحقيقي للقصف.
Wu Wancheng,
وو وانشنغ ،
Brother Wu did get up for the night yesterday,
لقد استيقظ الأخ وو ليلة أمس ،
But Brother Wu
لكن الأخ وو
ran out of explosives last time.
نفدت المتفجرات في المرة الماضية.
It better not be you.
من الأفضل ألا تكون أنت.
It's not too late if you apologize to me now.
لم يفت الأوان إذا اعتذرت لي الآن.
But if you lie to me,
لكن إذا كذبت علي
in fact, I'm
في الحقيقة أنا
Wu Wancheng. Mr. Tang Wenqi
وو وانشنغ ، السيد تانغ وينكي
asked you to look for him in the study.
طلب منك البحث عنه في الدراسة.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Let's make it clear to him tonight.
دعونا نوضح له هذه الليلة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
It's all your fault.
هذا كله خطأك.
If you hadn't suddenly appeared,
إذا لم تظهر فجأة ،
I would have sold my onion juice,
كنت سأبيع عصير البصل ،
If you sell my magic ink,
إذا قمت ببيع حبر سحري ،
you won't be punished.
لن يتم معاقبتك.
Why do you blame me?
لماذا تلومني؟
If you hadn't lied to me,
إذا لم تكذب علي ،
would I have been implicated by you?
هل كنت قد تورطت من قبلك؟
Will I be punished?
هل سأعاقب؟
If you hadn't exposed me,
إذا لم تكشف لي ،
Neither of us will be punished.
لن يعاقب أي منا.
The mountain chief said
قال رئيس الجبل
you would be punished for playing tricks in the market.
ستتم معاقبتك على ممارسة الحيل في السوق.
My father also said,
قال والدي أيضا ،
you were punished for picking quarrels
لقد تمت معاقبتك لقيامك باختيار المشاجرات
and making trouble in class. I'm too lazy
ويثير المتاعب في الفصل.  أنا كسول جدا
to argue with you if I can't explain it to you clearly.
لأتجادل معك إذا لم أتمكن من شرح ذلك لك بوضوح.
I don't need to talk to you.
لست بحاجة للتحدث معك.
They only rely on power and bully others.
إنهم يعتمدون فقط على السلطة ويتنمرون على الآخرين.
Why don't you two say hello to him?
لماذا لا تقولي لهما التحية؟